findstuff.com 2008-06-16

# FindStuff.com - Privacy Policy

**FindStuff Privacy Policy**

FindStuff respects the value of your privacy.

Information You Give Us.

The use of certain features and services on the FindStuff may require that you register and supply personally identifiable information (ex. wishlists) such as your name, email address, telephone number and other information, which is stored by FindStuff.com. When you register as a member, we may also collect additional information from you in order to provide you with those specific services and to personalize your experience on the FindStuff. This information is strictly optional. FindStuff does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, with your permission.

**Anti-Spam Policy**

FindStuff.com is vehemently opposed to unsolicited bulk email aka spam. We do not send emails to anyone without permission and we do not sell or provide email addresses to any unauthorized third party. We hate spam as much as you do. While we cannot prevent spam, if you think you have received an unsolicited email from us, please contact our Privacy Department and we will investigate.

**Cookies**

FindStuff.com uses "cookies" to automatically recognize returning users. A cookie is a small file on your hard drive that allows us to display your site preferences and search criteria on FindStuff.Cookies used by FindStuff may contain your user name, email address, IP address or zip code. Your internet service provider (ISP) assigns an internet protocol address (IP Address) to your computer when you use the Internet. We collect each IP address that accesses FindStuff, computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; your behavior on FindStuff and related services, including the products and merchants you view or searched for, as well as the URL you come from and go to next and cookie number. We use this information, as well as other data in our databases, to analyze site and user behavior, troubleshoot technical problems, address complaints prepare aggregated reports that we share with others and customize your experience on FindStuff.com. You can block cookies by changing the settings on your browser (contact your network administrator for help), but doing so may prevent us from delivering certain services to you (ex. wish lists).

**Minors**

FindStuff is not targeted towards, or intended for use by anyone under the age of 18. By using FindStuff you represent and warrant that you are 18 years of age or older. We reserve the right to terminate your membership in the event that FindStuff becomes aware you are under 18. Persons under 18 may not submit any personally identifiable information to us, and if we discover that we have inadvertently gathered such information, we will take the appropriate steps to delete it.

For all privacy questions, comments or concerns, please use our feedback form
